(Penny:)No.
You'll wish it would kill you.
(Amy:)So what do we do now?
(Leonard:)They have
some board games.
(Sheldon:)Eh, most of the Jenga
pieces are missing
(Sheldon:)and the Scrabble
only has seven tiles,
(Sheldon:)so unless you want to build
an unimpressive structure
with the word "SHNERPF"
next to it, move on.
(Penny:)Hey, let's light a fire.
(Amy:)Ooh, that sounds cozy.
(Bernadette:)I don't think
I've lit a real fire before.
(Sheldon:)Ah, it's basic thermodynamics.
(Sheldon:)I'm sure we can figure that out.
(Leonard:)I could stack the logs conically
to facilitate airflow.
(Sheldon:)That would maximize oxygen
for optimal combustion.
(fire whooshes)
Right. So all we need is to...
(Penny:)Got it.
(Leonard:)A scientist made that.
(Howard:)Look, Raj, you're my
best friend in the world
(Howard:)and I really appreciate
your enthusiasm about the baby.
(Raj:)Please, my pleasure.
(Bernadette:)And, of course,
Howie and I
(Bernadette:)both want you to be
a part of all this.
(Howard:)But we have to set
some boundaries.